Asta, Noel, and Magna traveled to Saucy Village to rid the area of Borg.
There they encountered a mysterious foe.
Though the three magic knights fight bravely to protect the villagers from the enemy's vicious attacks,
his magic power is far too great for even their strongest efforts.
So it can not only cancel magic, that sword of yours can reflect it as well.
But you're a fool if you think that will defeat me.
I can create wave after wave of icy fangs.
Go on. Let's see you protect them.
Damn this guy!
Asta and I have our hands full, keeping the villagers safe.
Once more, my magic is starting to run out.
This is turning out to be a hell of a first mission for those two.
Things are going south quick.
But if all that was enough to make me give up, I wouldn't be a man!
Here we go!
Your fellow commoner is gonna keep you safe and sound!
What's wrong with me?
Even though I'm royalty, even though I have more magic power than anyone here...
Stay behind us, Noelle!
I'm only holding the others back.
Miss Magic Knight, please help us!
We need you!
This little girl is looking me in the eye and begging for help.
I have to protect her!
I won't run!
Never!
That looks like... a new spell?
Water creation magic.
Sea Dragon's Lair!
A grimoire evolves along with its owner, new spells appearing as the mage grows stronger.
This growth chiefly refers to an increase in magic power through training or to improved handling of said magic power.
However, it may also occur in cases of heightened or altered emotions or accompany great determination.
I will protect them!
I am royalty!
What's more, I am a member of the Black Bulls!
name is the name of the Black Bulls!
Do you see the name of Black Bulls?
Wait till I was été pr限定 bye-bye.
cent of strophe strophe by hand
This words calm.
It cannot completely not sound.
My philosophy embr acad ład.
Oh!
Wholadı gall be?
Go!
Want?
част
Save us
It's
refusing
Find us
학
Eat
It's
The
ball
I'll never see this
There will be still
As well
The
people
You
Can
比
All
High
I'll see
Good night, Good day.
You're amazing.
Well, that wasn't so difficult after all.
That is one serious spell.
There, see?
You'll never know what you're capable of until you're willing to give it a try.
That's impossible.
How can she have so much power?
On the sidelines, the beast was watching, waiting for his chance to strike, to seize the enemy by the throat.
And in that moment...
Consider yourself.
You have enough magic power to have joined the Magic Knights.
I don't have a single drop of magic power.
But that doesn't matter!
I'll still destroy you!
What?
No, Master Heath!
That's what I'm talking about!
Did...
He get him?
Oh, no!
I slipped on his ice and killed my momentum!
That sword of yours may be able to nullify magic, but that can only go so far when it's wielded by an ordinary human.
Now it's my turn to take a stab at you.
Sleep, little fool.
For all eternity.
I'll stop.
There is tremendous magic power behind this spell.
Still, it's just a matter of time.
I ought to be able to create an entrance wide enough for at least one person to pass through.
This should take approximately 25 seconds.
You pesky creature certainly do enjoy wasting my time, don't you?
But oh, the price you will pay.
I don't have much magic power left.
I can't give up!
Flame and ice!
Going by our magic attributes, I have the upper hand!
Still, the difference in our power is enough to flip that on its head.
We picked the wrong guy to take on.
I'm sorry, Yamis, but I think this may be one fight that I can't win.
I'm not done yet!
Too late.
Asta!
So that last strike didn't kill you off.
You're a tough little idiot.
However, your wounds will make swinging that sword difficult.
Okay.
I'm not done!
And I'm no bore to be pinned.
I'm not done yet!
Got that?
How persistent.
But you're going to regret wasting my time.
You're amazing, Magna!
I never thought I'd see the day.
I can't believe there's going to be a real magic night from sleepy little Ryaka.
From street thug to the village's golden boy.
Let's give him a cheer!
Magna!
Really?
You did it, huh?
Wonderful.
I knew that you could make the cut.
Yeah.
This means you're not just some street punk anymore.
Well, go on.
Take it.
Uh, thanks.
What you think?
Mm-hmm.
It looks good on you, all right.
Now, go be the man I know you can be.
Right.
I've got this.
I'll do it, Zehi.
I'm not going to give up yet.
A real man hangs on to the bitter end.
Noelle, this spell of yours.
We can get outside of it easily enough, right?
Well, yes, I would imagine so.
You stay here and look after the villagers.
Got it?
Hey, what are you doing?
You stand no chance of prevailing against me.
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then who would protect them?
I realized something.
Hmm?
Sooner or later, I'm going to be the Wizard King.
But it's not just about keeping a promise.
It's about keeping people safe.
You think you'll be the Wizard King?
What an utterly ridiculous dream.
Especially considering that you'll be dead in one minute.
That's not going to happen, Frosty!
If you want to go after him, just try it!
I'll give you fair warning, though.
In order to do that, you've got to go through me!
What are you doing, Magna?
You and me?
We're the real men here, Asta.
Reckless fool.
Going out of your way to die an early death.
You have 30 seconds.
Bring it on!
You ready, Asta?
Time for a baptism.
Here we go!
All the magic power I've got now!
You have my soul ball!
Flame magic!
Prison deck!
Scatter shots!
This is the final spell of your pathetic life?
What a complete waste.
Your time is up.
You wish!
That wasn't the real attack.
He's reflecting the spell!
I'm alive.
You can thank me for it later, lonely street punk.
Oh my gosh, I did it!
I actually controlled my magic power!
Never can keep your mouth shut, can you?
These flames...
They aren't going out!
No matter.
I'll just freeze them.
Not done yet!
As long as I can still move, I'm not done!
No, you can't!
Like hell!
Yeah!
No, you can't!
No!
Impossible!
Me bested.
And by the way, I'm not going out!
No matter.
I'll just freeze them.
Not done yet!
As long as I can still move, I'm not done!
No!
You can't!
Like hell!
No!
Impossible.
Me bested.
And by this boy.
If only I could have been more use to the master.
But...
He did it.
Are we safe?
Yes.
He can't hurt you now.
It's over.
He did it.
Are we safe?
Yes.
He can't hurt you now.
It's over.
What started as Flame Magic Prison Death Scattershot will now become Flame Binding Magic! Flame Bondage Formation!
You're better at this than you'd look like you'd be. I can give you that much anyway.
How about you shut that royal mouth of yours and quit looking down on your superior?!
Once again, you just happen to be below me, so...
Magnus, sir!
Seems your follow-through leaves much to be desired, sir.
No!
Yes, really!
What was that about follow-through?!
I can't believe one of them got away!
How'd that happen?!
Damn it!
How do you like that?
I may be a commoner...
...but I won!
Yeah!
How do you like that?!
How do you like that?
Hey, man, are you all right?
Sleeping? Seriously?
He is such a fool, and a reckless one at that.
An idiotic, obnoxiously loud commoner.
But he's also kind of amazing.
He saved us. I thought we were done for.
He's still just a kid, too.
Do you think he's really just a commoner like us?
Thanks, Magna. And you miss for everything.
Sure, that's why we're here.
We're simply doing our duty.
Still, we'll never forget what you did for us.
What? An anti-bird?
Yeah, copy that.
bak!
Nah...
Ha, ha!
Ha-ha.
Hey!
About time you woke up, you sadistic jerks.
And now, we just gotta wait till my power comes back.
When it does, crazy cyclones hauling you to the capital.
Hmph.
You're gonna pay, I promise you.
You'll spend the rest of your lives making up for what you did today.
This spell of his appears to be blocking my magic.
Just wait, you're gonna spill everything.
Who you people are, what you're after.
The magic knights will get every last scrap of information out of you!
They will not.
The end times are upon us.
He's got a magic item inside him.
Engage ice magic, ice burial.
They were willing to go that far.
Must have sworn some serious loyalty to someone.
What was he thinking?
To sacrifice them all like that.
What was his game anyway?
How could they?
Treating life like it's something to throw away.
Like death is nothing.
I'll never understand these people.
Not in a million years.
Grandpa.
We should go home now.
Please, Vic.
And a bit, okay?
Grandpa always liked the view from up here.
Yeah.
I heard what happened.
Let's say he did.
He fought those men.
He did what he could to protect the village.
Huh?
Yeah.
Grandpa, we should go home now. Please, Vic.
In a bit, okay? Grandpa always liked the view from up here.
Yeah.
I heard what happened.
Let's say he did. He fought those men.
He did what he could to protect the village.
Huh?
Your grandpa was amazing. He was a real man.
You should have heard him tell the story about gambling in the capital.
He was so happy because he had beaten some magic knights.
Yeah.
He even used some of the money to buy presents.
And he brought lots of yummy food for everyone in the village to share.
He never got to become one.
But Grandpa would have loved to be a magic knight more than anything in the world.
Yeah, I know.
And he regretted it his whole life.
What did he regret?
He said he should have worked harder when he was young.
Then maybe his dream would have come true.
Nick.
But even though he didn't make it in, he was happy because you worked hard enough for the both of you.
Yeah.
Magna, could I?
Do you think?
Can I be a magic knight too someday?
Of course you can.
Just remember, nothing's impossible.
You can do anything, Nick.
Your future's what you make of it.
He's totally right.
I mean, I'm a commoner with no magic power.
And look at me now.
A knight!
It won't be easy.
Get ready to sweat.
You're gonna have to work hard.
And always do your best.
Just wait.
By the time you get into the magic knights, I'll have worked even harder, accomplished even more, and gotten even closer to becoming the wizard king.
Please, let's not get into that nonsense again.
But hey, point is dream big.
That's what a real man does.
We'll be waiting for you.
Got it?
Yeah!
Good.
Just what do you have against my head, feather brain?
Oh, it's on now!
I'll get you!
What's that stone?
Hey, I recognize that.
It's the charm Grandpa used to carry around with him.
Give it back, you!
Oh, this is something special!
Come on, bird, just let it go!
What do you even need a rock for?
It's okay.
Your bird can keep it if he wants to.
It's the least I can do after how you saved us.
Yeah?
Okay, thanks.
Just look at those hateful eyes.
He is so adorable!
You could sit on me if you'd like.
Not again!
You're pecking me, psycho bird!
What did I do to you?
Hey, get back here!
I'm going to fry you up for dinner!
Just leave me alone!
I'm going to...
Yeah!
Look at me!
So that's what Heath chose. Very well.
And the magic stone is now in the hands of the Black Bulls?
Yes, sir.
No matter. The Black Bulls won't be an issue. We can deal with them at any time.
They can keep the magic stone until we are ready to retrieve it.
Not long now. The resurrection is close at hand.
閉じた狭い教室で 今日も主役が輝いた 僕は眩しくて目を閉じる
散々考えた 革命は手の中に おかしいだろう
笑いたければ 笑えばいいから
残された僕らは 何かになりたくて
いつまでも いつまでも 同じ朝を迎えてる
明日を選ぶのは 君自身しかいらないよ
超えていこう 今日までの僕らを
The spittingest image. Go!
And the winner is This Anti-Bird
Just look how far you've come, Magna.
You're not just some punk anymore. You're a man.
You're on fire. Shining bright.
Black Clover. Page 11.
What happened on a certain day in the castle town?
My magic is never giving up.